Local 1199 Additional Files 5525
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Additional Files
1955-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199
5525
46.5 cubic feet
46.5 linear ft.
Case Files, primary sources.
Benefit plans, constitutions, correspondence, financial reports, activity and statistics reports and arbitration records
3121067
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5206: Local 1199 Records 5206-D: Local 1199 Drug Division Records 5206-G: Local 1199 Guild Division Records 5206-PR: Local 1199 President Leon Davis Records 5206-S: Local 1199 Executive Secretary Moe Foner Records 5206-X: Local 1199 Clippings and News Releases 5457: Mark Lillian Collection of Roosevelt Hospital (NYC) vs. Local 1199, 1962 Representational Dispute Documents 5510: Local 1199 Records 5520m: "Building a Union in the Hospitals: the Organization of Local 1199 at Montefoire Hospital, 1948-1958" Manuscript 5651: Local 1199 Additional Records 5768: Sidney Cahn Collection of League of Voluntary Hospitals & Homes of New York vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union Arbitration Files 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project 5854: Local 1199 Additional Records 5871: Local 1199 Additional Records 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5933: Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union News files 5933 P: Local 1199 Photograph Files 5938: Local 1199 Leon Davis Additional Papers 5945: Local 1199 Additional Records 5948: Local 1199 (Rochester, N.Y.) Records 5984 AV: Local 1199 Additional Videos 5984 AV: Local 1199 Additional Videos 6016: Local 1199 National Benefit and Pension Fund Records 6062: Paul Friedman Collection of National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199 Miscellany 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6140 P: Local 1199 Moe Foner Photographs 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files
National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees.; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.); Health facilities x Employees x Labor unions z United States x Sources.
3121067
- Adelphi Hospital, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Adelphi Hospital, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Affiliation Hospitals, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Benefit Plans, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Benefit Plans, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bronx - Planning Study, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Constitutions (Draft Proposals), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Constitutions (Draft Proposals), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Constitutions (Draft Proposals), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Constitutions (Draft Proposals), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Constitutions (Draft Proposals), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Contributions, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Contributions, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - Contributions, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Contributions, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Contributions, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Contributions, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Contributions, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Crank Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Foreign, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Foreign, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - General, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - General, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - General, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - General, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - General, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - General, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Membership, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Membership, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - Membership (District 1199), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Membership (District 1199), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Unions, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Davis, Leon - Personal, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Davis, Leon - Personal, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- District 1199 - Executive Council (Decisions, Political, General Correspondence), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- District 1199 - Memorandums, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Drug Pension Plan, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Economic Stabilization Program - Phase II, Phase III, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Economic Stabilization Program - Phase II, Phase III, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Executive Council - National Union, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Executive Council - National Union, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Hospital League - Local 1199 - Training and Upgrading, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Hospital League - Local 1199 - Training and Upgrading, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Hospital League - Local 1199 - Training and Upgrading, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Hospital Pension Plans, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Hospitals, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Hospitals, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Hospitals, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Hospitals, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Hospitals, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Incentive Systems, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Incentive Systems, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Incentive Systems, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Local 1199, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Local 1199, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Local 1199, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Local 1199C - Philadelphia, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Local 1199 - Credit Union, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Local 1199DC - Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Local 1199E - Baltimore, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Local 1199E - Baltimore, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Local 1199E - Baltimore, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Local 1199E - Baltimore, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Local 1199E - Baltimore, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Local 1199E - Baltimore, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Local 1199E - Baltimore, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Local 1199 - Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Local 1199 - Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Local 1199 - Housing Program, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Local 1199 - Housing Program, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Local 1199 - Housing Program, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Local 1199 - New Jersey, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Local 1199 - New Jersey, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Local 1199 - Pension Fund (Drug) Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Local 1199 - Retirees (& Tauber Camp & Scholarship), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Local 1199 - Retirees (& Tauber Camp & Scholarship), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Local 1199 - Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- National Union Convention, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- National Union Convention, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- National Union Convention, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- National Union Convention, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- New York City Central Labor Council, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- New York City Health and Hospital Corporation, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Office of Collective Bargaining, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Office of Collective Bargaining, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Pensions, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Personnel - Request for Employment, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Political Action, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Purchase Orders, etc., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Report on Phase III Controls (Humanic Designs Corp.), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Rollback - Affiliations, etc.., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Convention - National Union - New York, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Convention - National Union - New York, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Convention - National Union - New York, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Convention - National Union - New York, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Convention - National Union, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Convention - National Union, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Credentials, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Economic Stabilization Act - Legislation, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- 1199 Plaza Housing Dedication Ceremony, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Expo-Cuba Incident, July 26-29, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Foner, Moe - Vietnam Posters, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Grand Jury - Coalition to End G.J. Abuse, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Housing - Forest Hills, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Housing - 1199 Plaza, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Impeachment, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Installation - Officers, Organizers, and Delegates, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Labor Leadership for Peace, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Nixon Budget, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Rollback, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Strike - Helene Fund Hospital, Trenton, N.J., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Strike, 11/5/73, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Wage/Price Freeze, Phase II, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Wage/Price Freeze, Phase II and III, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Wage/Price Controls Phase IV, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Wage Freeze, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Monthly Activities Reports, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Monthly Activities Reports, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Monthly Activities Reports, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Monthly Activities Reports, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Monthly Activities Reports, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Arbitrations A - B (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Arbitrations C - D (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Arbitrations E - G (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Arbitrations H (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Arbitrations I - M (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Arbitrations N - R (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Arbitrations S -Z (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Impartial Arbitrators Correspondence (Burton B. Turkus, Esq.) (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Marrud, Inc. Arbitrations (Box 32, Folder 4)
- A - Bre (Box 33, Folder 1-End)
- Bri - Dil (Box 34, Folder 1-End)
- Dri - Fu (Box 35, Folder 1-End)
- G - H (Box 36, Folder 1-End)
- I - Li (Box 37, Folder 1-End)
- Li - Mu (Box 38, Folder 1-End)
- N - Ray (Box 39, Folder 1-End)
- Red - Sav (Box 40, Folder 1-End)
- Sax - Tru (Box 41, Folder 1-End)
- Tu - Zu (Box 42, Folder 1-End)
- Betha Abraham Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Bronx-Lebanon Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Cedar Manor Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Center Manor Nursing Home, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Community General Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Einstein, Albert Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Elmwood Manor Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Home and Hospital of Daughters of Jacob, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- House of the Holy Comforter, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Jewish Home and Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Montfiore Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- New Rochelle Hospital, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Northern Westchester Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Richmond Children's Center, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- St. Barnabas Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Saw Mill River Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Sprainbrook Manor Nursing Home, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- United Hebrew Home, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- United Odd Fellows Home, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Woodland Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Adelphi Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Brookdale Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Eye and Ear Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Methodist Church Home, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Charles Drew Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Community Hospital of Brooklyn, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Haym Solomon Home for the Aged, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Kingsbrook Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Lemberger Home for the Aged, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Lutheran Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Lutheran Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Maimonides Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Methodist-Carson Peck Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Richmond Memorial Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Staten Island Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- St. John's Episcopal Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- St. Mary's Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Sephardic Home for the Aged, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Unity Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Adams House, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Brentwood Manor, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Colchester Convalescent Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Community Health Service, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Dr. Friedman's Convalescent Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Danbury Pavilion, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Eden Park (empty folder), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Elmcrest Manor, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Greenwood Convalescent Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- High Ridge Convalescent Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Hilldale Convalescent Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Meadowbrook Convalescent Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Mt. Laurel Manor, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Pond Point, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Royal Crest, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- St. Mary's Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Seaside Convalescent Home, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Southport Manor, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- University of Bridgeport Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Waterbury Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Westport Manor, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- West Haven Manor, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Windorer, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Yale-New Haven Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Ardeon, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Beekman Hospital, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Beth Israel Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Columbus Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- French Benevolent Society, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Home of the Sages, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- N.Y. University Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- N.Y. Infirmary Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- ARA Jersey City Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Berkley Hall Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Beth Israel of Newark, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Bloomfield, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Brookwood Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Brunswick Park Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- CCL Englewood, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Clara Maass Memorial Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Cornell Hall Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Daughters of Israel, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Daughters of Miriam Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Daughters of Miriam Apartment House, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Elizabeth Manor Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Helene Fund Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Hillcrest Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Hospital Center of Orange, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Irvington Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Kleenrite, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Jersey City Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Jewish Hospital and Rehabilitation Center, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Memorial Center for Women, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Mountainside Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Northfield Manor Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Old Atlantic Hospital, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Parkway Nursing Home, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Pine Acres Nursing Home, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Princeton Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Saddle Brook Convalescent Home, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- St. Barnabas Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- St. Mary's Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- St. Michael's Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Workmen's Circle Old Age Home, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Bel Air Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Birchwood Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Booth Memorial Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Clinton Nursing Home, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Flushing Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Forest Manor, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Freeport Hospital, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Grace Plaza Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Hempstead General Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Hilaire Farm Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Hillside Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Jewish Institute of Geriatric Care, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Little Flower Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Manhasset Medical Center Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Montclair Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Patchoque Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Peninsula General Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Ross Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- St. John's Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Sayville Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Seagrit Village, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Smithtown Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- South Oaks Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Southampton Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- South shore Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Southside Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Sunrise Manor, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Syosset Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Todd Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- United Presbyterian Residence, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Westhampton Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Woodbury Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Amsterdam Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Association Residence for Women, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Columbia University Cafeterias, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Gracie Square Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Horn and Hardart, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Isabella Home, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Joint Diseases Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Lenox Hill Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- A.C. Logan Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Manhattan Eye, Ear, and Throat Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Mary Manning Walsh Home, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Presbyterian Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Trafalgar Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Yeshiva University, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Bronx-West, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Bronx-West, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Connecticut, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Connecticut, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Downtown, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- New Jersey, 1972-1974 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Queens-Long Island, 1972-1974 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Queens-Long Island, 1972-1974 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Uptown-East, 1972-1974 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Uptown-West, 1972-1974 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- NRLB Files, 1970-1974 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- NRLB Files, 1970-1974 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- NRLB Files, 1970-1974 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- NRLB Files, 1970-1974 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Association Residence for Women, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Booth Memorial Hospital, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Hospital, 1964-1971 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Methodist Church Home, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Central Suffolk Hospital, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Columbus Hospital, 1960-1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital, 1966-1968 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Evangelical Home for the Aged, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Hillside Hospital, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Home for Old Men and Aged Couples, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Home of the Sages of Israel, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Josephine Baird Home, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Mary Manning Walsh Home, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Northern Westchester Hospital, 1972-1974 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Park Crescent Nursing Home, 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1960-1967 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1960-1967 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1960-1967 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1960-1967 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1960-1967 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1960-1967 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Roosevelt Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- St. John's Queens Hospital, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1963-1967 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1963-1967 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1963-1967 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1963-1967 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1963-1967 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1968-1972 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- St. Lukes Hospital, 1968-1972 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- St. Lukes Hospital - General (Box 62, Folder 3)
- St. Lukes Hospital - General (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Stony Brook College, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Adams House - Torrington, 1970-1971 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Alliance Medical Inns, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Alliance Medical Inns, Inc., Stratford, etc., 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 3)